finprotrading.com 2018-08-03

# Privacy Policy and Legal | FinPro Trading

###  Privacy  Policy 

  * This privacy policy sets out how finprotrading.com uses and protects any information that you may give while using this website. Finprotrading.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Finprotrading.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from Jan 1, 2012. 

####  What we collect & How we use this information? 

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. 
  * To quickly process your transactions 
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services. 
  * We may contact you by email, (phone, fax or mail when available). 

####  Security 

  * We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

####  Note regarding Google Analytics Advertising Features. 

  * To better understand who our users are we enabled "Demographics and Interest Reports" - the part of Google Analytics Advertising Features. Google Analytics does not collect any Personally Identifiable Information including (but not limited to) names, email addresses or billing information. 
  * Finprotrading.com users that don't want their data reported by the Google can install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. 

####  Controlling your personal information. 

  * You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information by not filling any forms on this website. If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us using contact us form at the bottom of the site pages with the request to modify or delete your personal information previously submitted to Finprotrading.com. 

####  How to Unsubscribe from our list. 

  * If you no longer wish to receive communications from Finprotrading.com, it’s very easy to stop. Simply scroll down to the bottom of any email and click the “unsubscribe” link. Every email that is sent from Finprotrading.com mailing list is specially coded with a link that is tied to your email subscription account. If you no longer wish to receive emails from Finprotrading.com, simply scroll to the bottom of the email and click the unsubscribe link. 

####  Details of Personal Information. 

  * We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please send us a message using contact us form at the bottom of the site pages. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

####  How do we protect visitor information? 

  * Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. 
  * We use regular Malware Scanning. 
  * Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 
  * We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. 
  * All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers. 

####  Legal 

  * Governing Law. All terms and conditions of this website are subject to and to be interpreted by the laws of the United Kingdom . Any disputes arising with regard to this website or its content will be brought only in the courts of the City of London. 

####  Cookie Policy. 

  * Be aware, much of the functionality of the Finprotrading.com site relies on cookies. If you continue to use this site, you are consenting to our use of cookies. You are always free to erase them after each visit. 

####  What Cookies Are 

  * Cookies are small files stored on your computer by your web browser (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox) at the request of a site you're viewing. This allows the site you're viewing to remember things about you, such as your preferences and history or to keep you logged in. 
  * Cookies may be stored on your computer for a short time (such as only while your browser is open) or for an extended period of time, even years. Cookies not set by this site will not be accessible to us. 

####  Our Cookie Usage 

  * This site uses cookies for numerous things, including: 
  * Registration and maintaining your preferences. This includes ensuring that you can stay logged in and keeping the site in the language or appearance that you requested. 
  * Analytics. This allows us to determine how people are using the site and improve it. 
  * Advertising cookies (possibly third-party). If this site displays advertising, cookies may be set by the advertisers to determine who has viewed an ad or similar things. These cookies may be set by third parties, in which case this site has no ability to read or write these cookies. 
  * Other third-party cookies for things like Facebook or Twitter sharing. These cookies will generally be set by the third-party independently, so this site will have no ability to access them. 

####  Removing/Disabling Cookies 

  * Managing your cookies and cookie preferences must be done from within your browser's options/preferences.
